const e="english",o=200,a=75,t=[{id:223,question:"The police claim that a number of stolen cars…… recovered ",option:{a:"have been ",b:"has been  ",c:"has being",d:" have being "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:224,question:"     ………….  been there to look for her several times without success.",option:{a:"He'll",b:"He’s  ",c:"Is he ",d:"He is"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:225,question:" Until he lost the election, Agbo…………… to be the Student Union president.",option:{a:"had been hoping ",b:"has been hoping   ",c:"would have hoped   ",d:" has hoped "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:226,question:"The old man was rushed to hospital when his blood  pressure dropped to a ……..  level",option:{a:"dangerously lowly",b:"dangerous lowly ",c:" dangerously low",d:" dangerous low"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:227,question:"If he ……… for admission, I am sure he would succeed",option:{a:"will apply ",b:"applied ",c:"had applied ",d:"has applied"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:228,question:"The ……….   robber showed no mercy during the attack. ",option:{a:"loquacious ",b:"senseless ",c:"ruthless ",d:"benevolent"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:229,question:"Did you have ……… when you went to visit the medical doctor? ",option:{a:"diarrhea ",b:"diarrhea",c:"diarhoea  ",d:"diarrhea "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:230,question:"Your performance will improve if you…….  Hard",option:{a:"are practicing ",b:"practical ",c:"would practice ",d:"practise"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:231,question:"The brave hunter killed the ………… in the forest ",option:{a:"big spitting cobra black",b:"Black big spitting cobra ",c:"big black spitting cobra ",d:"big spitting black cobra "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:232,question:"He wrote to you,……….  ?",option:{a:"hadn’t he ",b:"wouldn’t  he ",c:"didn’t he",d:"hasn’t he"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:233,question:"The clubs were not…….. on a solid ethical base ",option:{a:"funded",b:"found ",c:"created ",d:"founded "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:234,question:"I watched him as he……  the hole",option:{a:"dug ",b:"digs",c:"is digging ",d:"dugged"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:235,question:"His father hardly misses the news because he goes about with his………..  Radio",option:{a:"pointable ",b:"potable ",c:"potable",d:"portable"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:236,question:"The investigation Commission has treated all the …… submitted to it by the warring factions",option:{a:"protests ",b:"petitions ",c:"applications",d:"enquires "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:237,question:"Olu brought his clothes and those of his………..",option:{a:"Senior brother’s",b:"elder brothers",c:"elder brother’s ",d:"senior brother."},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:238,question:"Our neigbour was attracted by the ………. from my mother’s cooking ",option:{a:"flavour",b:"stench",c:"scent",d:"aroma "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:239,question:"Everybody is allowed to ………. his views on state matters ",option:{a:"Air ",b:"hear ",c:"show ",d:"share "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:240,question:"Despite all preparations, the wedding did not …..",option:{a:"come along ",b:"come by",c:"come on ",d:"come off"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:241,question:"For beating ……. his course mate, Agbaji was……… from the university.",option:{a:"up/rusticated ",b:"on/expelled",c:"at/removed ",d:"away/sent out "},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:242,question:"We have been living peacefully here but……….. hear rumours of war.",option:{a:"again ",b:"slowly",c:"occasionally ",d:"eventually"},section:"choose the option that best completes the gap(s).",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:243,question:"Genealogy ",option:{a:"GeneaLOGY",b:"geneAlogy",c:"geNEalogy ",d:"GEnealogy "},section:"choose the appropriate stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"b ",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:244,question:"Catholicism ",option:{a:"caTHOlicism ",b:"catholiCism",c:"CAtholicism ",d:"cathoLIcism "},section:"choose the appropriate stress pattern from the options. The syllables are written in capital letters.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:245,question:"",option:{a:"ability ",b:"Registration ",c:" quadruplicate ",d:"revivalist "},section:"choose the option that has a different stress pattern from the others. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:246,question:"",option:{a:"competent ",b:"represent ",c:" syllabus ",d:"quality "},section:"choose the option that has a different stress pattern from the others. ",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:247,question:"apparent ",option:{a:"arrested ",b:"telephone ",c:"paragraph ",d:"appetite "},section:"choose the option that has the same stress pattern as the given word.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:248,question:"Unfair ",option:{a:"insight ",b:"towards ",c:"first-class",d:"instant "},section:"choose the option that has the same stress pattern as the given word.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:249,question:"Dovetail ",option:{a:"proviso ",b:"simplicity ",c:"jargon ",d:"psychiatry "},section:"choose the option that has the same stress pattern as the given word.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:250,question:"",option:{a:" Insult (noun)",b:"prepare ",c:" provoke",d:"pronounce "},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:251,question:"",option:{a:"Frequent (verb)",b:"mature ",c:"madam",d:"convict (verb)"},section:"choose the option that has the stress on the first syllable.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:252,question:"In our college, the regulations concerning resists are a grey area",option:{a:"The regulations have just been revised",b:"The regulations have often been ignored",c:"The regulations are perfectly clear",d:"The regulations are not very clear."},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:253,question:"Ogiri takes after his father, he fawns upon anyone with influence.",option:{a:"Like his father, Ogiri likes to flatter people with influence in society",b:"Like his father, Ogiri hates influential people",c:"Ogiri. who always follows his father, tries to act like an influential man",d:"Ogiri, who looks like his father, follows rich and influential people about"},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:254,question:"You are to write a report and give it to the security office",option:{a:"After writing your report, give it to the security office",b:"You are writing a report, as the security office directed",c:"The report you are writing should be given to the security office",d:"You have been ordered to write a report, which you wilt give to the security office "},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:255,question:"After the war the victors became Increasingly vindictive ",option:{a:"Vengeful attacks were Incessantly carried out on those who lost the war ",b:"  Friendly measures were taken to heal the wounds",c:"Repressive measures were taken against those who lost the war",d:"Those who won the war became treacherous "},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:256,question:"The prefect reeled off the names of all the students who Drake the library law.",option:{a:"The prefect gave a disjointed list of the students in the law library.",b:"  The prefect omitted the names of the students who broke into the law library ",c:"The prefect submitted a complete list of the students who stole library books",d:"The prefect gave an accurate list of the students who disobeyed library regulations."},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:257,question:"1 owe you far less than you owe me",option:{a:"My debt to you is greater than yours to me",b:"Your debt is not much greater than mine",c:"What we owe each other Is approximately the same",d:"I owe you something, but you owe me much more"},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:258,question:"The dispute over land acquisition has now come a head",option:{a:"The problem has reached crisis proportions ",b:"The problem has now been referred to the headquarters ",c:"Because of the dispute, land acquisition has now been halted ",d:"The problem has now been solved "},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:259,question:"He has hardly spoken when the bell rang ",option:{a:"He found it difficult to speak, and then the bell rang",b:"When the bell rang, he was still speaking ",c:"The bell rang very soon after he spoke",d:"He spoke in a harsh manner and the bell rang "},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:260,question:"I think she takes her guardian’s support for granted ",option:{a:"Her guardian has been helping her for a long time, and she is very grateful to him. ",b:"She wants her guardian to grant her more support.",c:"She thinks her guardian will no longer support her as he has been doing.",d:" Her guardian has been helping her for a long time, but she does not show enough gratitude. "},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:261,question:"The class has fallen in with the teacher's plans",option:{a:"The class has ignored the plans",b:"The class has rejected the plans",c:" The class has accepted the plans",d:"The class has modified the plans"},section:"the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence. ",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:262,question:"The move to expel the chairman was <i>sanctioned</i> by members of the party       ",option:{a:"unleashed  ",b:"opposed ",c:"supported",d:" initiated"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:263,question:"Because Jamiu is so <i>easily offended,</i> he was not considered for the post of headboy",option:{a:"Irritable    ",b:"stubborn   ",c:"troublesome ",d:"docile"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:264,question:"The witness provided a <i>monstrous</i> account of the event",option:{a:"supportive  ",b:"tragic",c:"shocking ",d:"verbatim"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:265,question:"Adamu is rather <i>meddlesome</i> in dealing with his friends",option:{a:"impertinent ",b:"intimidating ",c:"quarrelsome",d:" uncaring"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:266,question:"The commander said that the battle would be sustained, total and <i>relentless</i>",option:{a:"continuous ",b:"brutal   ",c:"fierce ",d:"innocuous"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:267,question:"The government has announced its <i>preparedness for</i> the scheme",option:{a:"determination ",b:"regret ",c:"pleasure ",d:"readiness"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:268,question:"The chairman advised the participants to follow <i>convention</i> in stating their points.",option:{a:"eloquence ",b:"advice ",c:"prudence ",d:"tradition"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:269,question:"His discovery of the vaccine became a <i>quantum leap</i> in the search for a scientific cure for the illness",option:{a:"victorious battle ",b:"slow but steady step",c:" great improvement   ",d:"fast but sure step"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:270,question:"After the meeting, I read a <i>leer</i> on his face as he looked at the woman.   ",option:{a:"satisfying meaning ",b:"bad look ",c:"pleasant disposition ",d:"poor smile"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:271,question:"His loss suddenly became <i>redeemable</i> ",option:{a:"Incurable  ",b:"exclusive",c:"recoverable ",d:"repulsive"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:272,question:"The plan has gone <i>awry</i>",option:{a:"wide   ",b:"wrong   ",c:"well    ",d:" wild"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:273,question:"The judge emphasized his <i>morbid</i> desire in his judgement",option:{a:"inordinate ",b:"uncritical ",c:"ravenous ",d:" Unpleasant"},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:274,question:"77. The recommended novel has a <i>convoluted</i> theme",option:{a:" a simple ",b:"an attractive ",c:"a disgusting ",d:"a complicated "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:275,question:"The party men <i>reveled</i> all night when the election results were announced.",option:{a:"Celebrated ",b:"mourned",c:"fought ",d:"discussed "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:276,question:"He is <i>prolific</i>  writer ",option:{a:"a very productive",b:"a well-known",c:"a clever ",d:"an influential "},section:"choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:277,question:"h<u>ur</u>t",option:{a:"hut ",b:"girl ",c:"hate   ",d:"hot"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:278,question:"c<u>o</u>ck",option:{a:"cop   ",b:"cope ",c:"cork ",d:"cup"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:279,question:"s<u>ay</u>s",option:{a:"fierce  ",b:"dam",c:"wet",d:"rain"},section:"choose the option that has the same vowel sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:280,question:"c<u>h</u>aracter",option:{a:"unique   ",b:"charade   ",c:"arch   ",d:"church "},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:281,question:"  bush<u>es</u>",option:{a:"shapes ",b:"shoes  ",c:"rapes   ",d:"rakes"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:282,question:"gara<u>ge</u>",option:{a:"gear   ",b:"sure   ",c:"pressure ",d:"measure"},section:"choose the option that has the same consonant sound as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:283,question:"The usually hostile crowd was captivated by the .player's <i>winsome</i> attitude",option:{a:"obnoxious  ",b:"friendly  ",c:"colourful  ",d:"drunken"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:284,question:"The reporter made a <i>masterly</i> analysis of the situation",option:{a:"an unskilful ",b:"a mistaken ",c:"an indepth",d:"a proper"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:285,question:"He has no reason to <i>have his heart in his mouth</i>",option:{a:" think negatively",b:" feel guilty ",c:" be afraid",d:" be confident"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:286,question:"That little boy has become quite <i>chubby</i>",option:{a:"thin    ",b:" intelligent   ",c:"huge    ",d:"tall"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:287,question:"Akpan was able to <i>douse</i> the flames with the new piece of equipment",option:{a:"reduce ",b:"extinguish ",c:"ignite ",d:"reinforce"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:288,question:"He gave himself up by his <i>plebeian</i> tastes",option:{a:"robust ",b:"voracious ",c:"patrician   ",d:"laughable"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:289,question:"<i>No sooner had</i> he arrived than it started to rain",option:{a:" Long before ",b:" Seldom ",c:"Simultaneously",d:"Just before"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:290,question:"The action was <i>premeditated</i>",option:{a:"unnecessary ",b:"catastrophic ",c:"unplanned ",d:"uncoordinated"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:291,question:"A <i>tentative</i> solution was provided",option:{a:"A convincing ",b:" provisional",c:"An amicable ",d:"A definite"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:292,question:"The chief said he would use the power <i>inherent</i> in his office to stop the celebration",option:{a:" unrelated to ",b:" common to ",c:" allotted to ",d:" impervious to"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:293,question:"In our last play, Segun acted the <i>hero</i>",option:{a:"villain  ",b:" devil ",c:"criminal ",d:" assassin"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:294,question:"The police found a <i>conclusive</i> proof of the boy's guilt",option:{a:"a corroborative ",b:"A doubtful ",c:"a consolatory",d:" an incriminating"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:295,question:"The point you have made is quite <i>apt</i>",option:{a:"illogical ",b:"helpful ",c:"irrelevant ",d:"insensitive"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:296,question:"The man drew a sword as people <i>congregated round</i> him",option:{a:"praised",b:" gathered round ",c:" mobbed ",d:" fled from"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:297,question:"The notice reads, No <i>cash</i> transactions in this hall'",option:{a:"money   ",b:"gainful ",c:"business ",d:"cheque"},section:"choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics.",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2006",questionNub:null,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],s={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
